{
    "id": "76b29010a4ca44bdabca876acfb683d4",
    "title": "Noun Clauses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "............................... he said is of no importance to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "That",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1bb3ec66c35c4f948d7a26f1a1cec10d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The king said ..................................... his minister deserved to be honored.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "how"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "188156c20a8a482fba8cf32df69ab7e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The news ................................. all was well delighted everyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "how",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "821bcacf254a4450968aebcbfc09b90b"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is interesting to notice ...................................... soon birds learn the danger of electric wires.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "how",
                "why",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "37431e6118cc489a99998fd4b52151b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The bench of judges declared .................................... the accused was not guilty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "how"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "618a10c0727045188981aaccfc00c972"
        },
        {
            "question": "The report ..................................... only ten persons were killed in the explosion is not true.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "how"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fe8e7e0f6548405ab4cae1e44a7f1765"
        },
        {
            "question": "I want to know ..................................... far the station is from here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "how",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "663badcd4b124d3bb16a739f6074233c"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is strongly rumored ...................................... plague has broken out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "why"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cb7567fbab804011b04eed1889cac008"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said ...................................... his sister was ill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "how"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9c3bbc4523354cb6affa64a30cd7b38b"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is strange ...................................... you should think so.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "how"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "091a610fbfdc429aa583f015bfbc8cba"
        }
    ]
}